<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Insightic - Web3 Compliance Made Easy</title><link>https://insightic.io/</link><description>Recent content on Insightic - Web3 Compliance Made Easy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://insightic.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Community Resource - BINANCE</title><link>https://insightic.io/blog/community-resource-binance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/blog/community-resource-binance/</guid><description>About Binance Holdings Ltd., also referred to as Binance, is the largest exchange in the world offering a platform for selling and buying cryptocurrency for the traders and users. The company is found by Changpeng Zhao (CZ) and Yi He in China in 2017. Soon after its establishment, Binance grows quickly and launches two cryptocurrencies, including Binance Coin (BNB), and BinanceUSD (BUSD). In 2023, Binance and CZ are under investigation by many governments, such as US, Canada, and Australia.</description></item><item><title>Community Resource - FTX</title><link>https://insightic.io/blog/community-resource-ftx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/blog/community-resource-ftx/</guid><description>About FTX was an international cryptocurrency exchange founded by Sam Bankman-Fried and Gary Wang in 2019. It grew to become one of the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world, and at its peak, was valued at USD25b in 2021. The rise of FTX came to a halt when a Nov 2022 CoinDesk report expressed risks of a collapse. Nine days after the report, FTX entered and remains in Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings in the US court system.</description></item><item><title>Mentorship Arrangement with Northern Trust and NUS AIDF</title><link>https://insightic.io/blog/mentorship-northern-trust-nus-aidf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/blog/mentorship-northern-trust-nus-aidf/</guid><description>We are thrilled to share that we are a mentored startup under a collaboration between Northern Trust and National University of Singapore’s Asian Institute of Digital Finance (“NUS AIDF”).
Northern Trust is one of the oldest and largest financial institutions in the world. Headquartered in the United States with operations across the globe, it provides asset servicing, asset management and wealth management services.
NUS AIDF is a university-level institute jointly founded by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (“MAS”), National Research Foundation (“NRF”) and NUS.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/contact-us/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/pre-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/pre-assessment/</guid><description>Pre-assessment AI-powered due diligence for virtual asset An AI agent to conduct an initial assessment of virtual asset service providers. This evidence-driven automation is designed not only to substantially minimize manual efforts in preliminary due diligence but also to offer better and more comprehensive coverage across various risk factors. A standout feature of our system is the distinctive de-anonymization technique, which not only unveils crucial insights but also ensures a thorough screening process.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/risk-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/risk-assessment/</guid><description> Risk Assessment Risk Examination for Web3 Projects Leveraging patent-pending graph analytics tools, we offer detailed analysis and constant monitoring of over 150 risk factors in the dynamic digital assets landscape. Our system identifies and recommends actions to remediate identified risks, encompassing areas from fraud detection to tokenomic and DAO assessments, providing a secure foundation for your initiatives. Coming soon!</description></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/smart-contract-validator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/smart-contract-validator/</guid><description>Smart Contract Validator Seamless validation and compliance with whitepaper and smart contracts Smart Contract Validator (SCV) is a tool utilized for cross-validation and examination of whitepapers and smart contracts. By scrutinizing the whitepaper and smart contract, SCV possesses the ability to uncover disparities between them and provide appropriate warnings. Step 1 Upload whitepaper Step 2 Upload Smart Contract code submit Smart Contract Validator - Results Job ID: {{ jobId }} Passed Risks Warnings Ignored Passed Hide {{ passed.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/wait/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/wait/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> Please wait for the result!</description></item></channel></rss>