<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Insightic - Web3 Compliance Made Easy</title><link>https://insightic.io/</link><description>Recent content on Insightic - Web3 Compliance Made Easy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://insightic.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Community Resource - FTX</title><link>https://insightic.io/blog/community-resource-ftx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/blog/community-resource-ftx/</guid><description>About FTX was an international cryptocurrency exchange founded by Sam Bankman-Fried and Gary Wang in 2019. It grew to become one of the biggest cryptocurrency exchange in the world, and at its peak, was valued at USD25b in 2021. The rise of FTX came to a halt when a Nov 2022 CoinDesk report expressed risks of a collapse. Nine days after the report, FTX entered and remains in Chapter 11 bankruptcy proceedings in the US court system.</description></item><item><title>Mentorship Arrangement with Northern Trust and NUS AIDF</title><link>https://insightic.io/blog/mentorship-northern-trust-nus-aidf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/blog/mentorship-northern-trust-nus-aidf/</guid><description>We are thrilled to share that we are a mentored startup under a collaboration between Northern Trust and National University of Singapore’s Asian Institute of Digital Finance (“NUS AIDF”).
Northern Trust is one of the oldest and largest financial institutions in the world. Headquartered in the United States with operations across the globe, it provides asset servicing, asset management and wealth management services.
NUS AIDF is a university-level institute jointly founded by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (“MAS”), National Research Foundation (“NRF”) and NUS.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/contact-us/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/smart-contract-validator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/smart-contract-validator/</guid><description> Smart Contract Validator Smart Contract Validator (SCV) is a tool utilized for cross-validation and examination of whitepapers and smart contracts. By scrutinizing the whitepaper and smart contract, SCV possesses the ability to uncover disparities between them and provide appropriate warnings. Step 1 Upload whitepaper Step 2 Upload Smart Contract code submit SCV - Results Job ID: {{ jobId }} Try again {{ title }} {{ description }} Whitepaper {{ whitepaper }} Code {{ code }} {{ result['description'] }} {{ result['pass'] }} Whitepaper {{ result['whitepaper'] }} Code {{ result['code'] }}</description></item><item><title/><link>https://insightic.io/wait/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://insightic.io/wait/</guid><description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html> Please wait for the result!</description></item></channel></rss>